{
    "subject": "resource/Ouzouer-sous-Bellegarde",
    "predicate": "ontology/region",
    "object": "resource/Centre-Val_de_Loire",
    "human_readable": "Ouzouer-sous-Bellegarde is located in Centre-Val de Loire.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9597921371459961,
            "question": "Where is Ouzouer-sous-Bellegarde located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8860605359077454,
            "question": "What type of place is Ouzouer-sous-Bellegarde?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8711287379264832,
            "question": "What region is Ouzouer-sous-Bellegarde in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8644991517066956,
            "question": "Are there any notable landmarks in Ouzouer-sous-Bellegarde?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8058351278305054,
            "question": "Can you name a city in Centre-Val de Loire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7752015590667725,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist attractions near Ouzouer-sous-Bellegarde?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7172443866729736,
            "question": "What are some other cities in Centre-Val de Loire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6225865483283997,
            "question": "Is Ouzouer-sous-Bellegarde part of France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5774699449539185,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Centre-Val de Loire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5739671587944031,
            "question": "How would you describe the culture of Centre-Val de Loire?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ouzouer-sous-Bellegarde is located in Centre-Val de Loire.",
            "html": "dbpedia_147_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Centre-Val de Loire?",
            "html": "dbpedia_147_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ouzouer-sous-Bellegarde part of France?",
            "html": "dbpedia_147_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some other cities in Centre-Val de Loire?",
            "html": "dbpedia_147_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_147_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_147_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_147_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_147_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_147_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_147_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_147_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_147_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_147_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_147_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe information provided mentions that Ouzouer-sous-Bellegarde is located in France, specifically in the department of Loiret and region Centre. While Centre-Val de Loire is a larger administrative region that includes the Centre region, it does not seem to be an exact match with the location mentioned in the context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Ouzouer-sous-Bellegarde is indeed located in the Centre-Val de Loire region of France."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It directly contradicts the information provided in context 1, which clearly states \"Find detailed maps for France Centre-Val de Loire Loiret Ouzouer-sous-Bellegarde\" and context 3, which states that the town of Ouzouer-sous-Bellegarde is located in the department of Loiret of the french region Centre.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}